http://www.spectralcore.com/privacy

Products
Full Convert
Convert your database to any popular database format.
Replicator
Compare the contents and synchronize your databases.
Omni Loader
Enterprise-class database migration cluster, handling petabytes.
SQL App
No-compromise PostgreSQL database manager.
Documenter
HTML documentation for all your databases
SQL Tran
Closed beta
Translation of all database code - procedures, functions, views, triggers...
Database migration service
Available now!
Let us handle everything for you and take advantage of our expertize. Pay per your data size.
Help
Help center
Find help articles here. Open a support ticket.
Databases we support
Wondering if we have what you need? Find out here.
Company
About us
Meet the team.
Contact
Need to talk with someone before purchasing? Need a demo?
Privacy Policy
This website privacy policy was last updated on August 13, 2020. The policy covers the following topics.
How We Protect Your Privacy
Information We Collect from You and Interest-Based Advertising.
1. How We Protect Your Privacy
This website privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. By visiting our website (SpectralCore.com), you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this website privacy policy. In particular, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this website privacy policy.
2. Information We Collect from You and Interest-Based Advertising.
Like most places on the Internet, simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information. This includes basic information such as your IP address, when you visited, the website from where you came prior to visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our website, your computer's operating system, and the type of web browser that you are using.
Our website automatically records this basic information about you.
And like many other websites, we may use cookies, digital fingerprinting (e.g. device, machine, and Internet browser fingerprints), web beacons, click redirects, pixel tags, container tags, and similar technologies. In plain English, this means information that our website's server transfers to your computer. This information can be used to track your session on our website and to customize our website content for you as an individual.
If you are using one of the common Internet Web browsers, you can set up your browser to either (a) let you know when you are being tracked by us or to (b) deny us tracking access to your computer or electronic mobile device. The manufacturer of the browser you use has instructions on how to modify tracking settings. You may find these instructions in the “Help” section of your browser or by contacting the browser’s manufacturer.
If you download or use our desktop software applications (“Desktop Apps”) or mobile software applications (“Mobile Apps”), we may know your location. In addition, your smart phone, computer tablet, desktop or other electronic device using our software applications may provide us information about the device, including its unique identifier, make and model, operating system, IP address, mobile network carrier, and your telephone number. Your mobile device may have the ability to disable location services as well as deny us access to other information described in this paragraph. To learn more, check your mobile device’s user manual and/or contact your mobile device’s manufacturer or service carrier.
We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our website or by sending to us via email. You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website's services and features.
Some transactions between you and our website may involve payment by credit card, debit card, checks, money orders, and/or third-party online payment services. In such transactions, we will collect information related to the transaction as part of the course of doing business with you, including your billing address, telephone number, and other information related to the transaction.
3. What We Do with Your Information
We use your information to operate our website's business activities. For example, we may use this data to contact you about changes to our website, direct marketing (e.g. new products and services, special offers, etc.), resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues, and enforce our website's terms and conditions.
Desktop and Mobile Applications
If you download or use Desktop Apps or Mobile Apps from our website, the information we learn about you may be used by us to give you personalized content based upon your location and other data you share. If you do not want to share your location via Desktop Apps or Mobile Apps, check the instruction manual for your electronic device or contact your device’s manufacturer to see if you can turn off the locator feature.
Your Information and Third Parties
As a general rule, we will not give your data to third parties without your permission. However, there are some important exceptions to this rule that are described in the following paragraphs.
Government & Law Enforcement
We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you to law enforcement or other government officials for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability.
Some government intelligence agencies have the technological ability to access data from our website without our cooperation, knowledge, or consent. Even if we were to learn of such access, we may not be able to tell you because of national security laws. Please take this risk into account before supplying information to us or any other website owner.
Data Disclosure to Third Parties
We will never sell our website's visitors’ data to advertisers or other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes.
If website ownership changes (e.g. by sale, bankruptcy, etc.), we may transfer your information to the new site owner. Upon completion of such a transfer, we will no longer possess or control the data received by the new owner.
4. Do-Not-Track, Remarketing, and Dynamic Ad Serving
Do-Not-Track
We try to honor any Do-Not-Track signals you send through your web browser when visiting our website. However, please read the following important information about “Interest-Based Advertising,” “Remarketing,” and “Dynamic Ad Serving” so that you understand the type of tracking that may be done by third party vendors when you visit our site and how you can opt out of such tracking.
Remarketing
This website may use a remarketing tag to advertise online. This means that Google and other third-party vendors may show our ads to you on sites across the Internet. These third-party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads to you based upon your past visits to our website.
Opting Out - Google Cookies
If you would like to opt out of Google’s use of cookies, you can visit the company’s Ad Preferences Manager at https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en.
Opting Out - Third Party Vendor Cookies
In the alternative, you can opt out of the use of cookies by some third-party vendors by going to the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page located at https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1.
Opting Out - Google Dynamic Ad Serving
Our website may use Google’s Dynamic Ad Serving feature. To opt out of interest-based ads by Google, follow Google’s opt-out instructions located at https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en .
Opting Out - Google DoubleClick Remarketing Pixels
Our website may use DoubleClick’s remarketing pixels. If you would like to opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies, you can visit the DoubleClick opt-out page at https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en#display_optout.
5. User Names And Passwords
Your access to parts of our website may be protected by a user name and a password. Do not give your password to anyone. If you enter a section of our website that requires a password, you should log out when you leave. As a safety precaution, you should also close out of your web browser completely and re-open it before viewing other parts of the Internet.
Use of Information and Unsolicited Commercial Email
If you obtain personally identifiable information about another website user, you are not allowed to disclose this information to anyone else without the consent of the user and our consent too. If you communicate with other website users via our website (or by other means), such third parties may have copies of your communications even if you delete your own copies of such communications on our website and your electronic devices.
We hate junk email (spam). Information you obtain from our website about us or other site users cannot be used by you or others to send unsolicited commercial email or to send unsolicited commercial communications via our website's posting or other communication systems.
Your Voluntary Disclosure of Information to Third Parties Who Are Not Our Suppliers
You may choose to provide personal information to website visitors or other third parties who are not our suppliers. Please use caution when doing so. The privacy policies and customs of these third parties determine what is done with your information.
6. Autoresponders
We may use autoresponders to communicate with you by email. To protect your privacy, we use a verified opt-in system for such communications and you can always opt-out of such communications using the links contained in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, you may contact us by using one of the contact methods listed on our Website’s “Contact” page at www.spectralcore.com/contact.
7. Information Security
We try to keep your information secure. If we become aware of a data vulnerability, where economically feasible, we will attempt to promptly fix it in order to keep your data safe. However, with governments spying online using sophisticated technology and hackers data mining sites, no website owner can guarantee your information will be completely safe from unauthorized access by others. Please take these security risks into account before giving information to us or any other website owner.
8. Data Retention
We will keep your data for as long as we need it to provide you with products and services, comply with applicable law, resolve any disputes between us or with third parties, and to enforce any contracts between us.
9. California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please contact us by using one of the contact methods listed on our Website’s “Contact” page at www.spectralcore.com/contact.
If you reside in the State of California, you may have certain privacy rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.100 to § 1798.199 ("CaCPA"). However, the CaCPA does not apply to us for one or more of the following reasons: (1) we are a small or medium-sized enterprise (“SME”) that is not a “business” as such term is defined in Subsection 1798.140(c) of the CaCPA; (2) other laws (e.g. United Kingdom laws) apply to us that conflict with and/or supersede the CaCPA.
Even though we do not have a legal obligation to do so, we may respond to your requests made per the CaCPA. However, these voluntary responses are not a waiver of our legal rights and obligations under the laws of the United Kingdom or the arbitration provisions found within our website’s Terms and Conditions of Use.
10. United Kingdom and European Union Privacy Rights
If you reside in the European Union, you may have certain privacy rights under Regulation (EU) 2016/679, the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR"), to the extent the GDPR does not conflict with the laws of the United Kingdom. Even if we do not have a legal obligation to do so under the laws of the United Kingdom, we may respond to your requests made per the GDPR. However, voluntary responses are not a waiver of our legal rights and obligations under the laws of the United Kingdom or the arbitration provisions found within our website’s Terms and Conditions of Use.
Small or Medium-Sized Enterprise Status
We are a small or medium-sized enterprise (“SME”). This means that because of the size of our business, to the extent (if any) the GDPR governs our relationship with you, some of GDPR’s obligations do not apply because we are an SME.
How to Make A Request
To make a GDPR request, please contact us by using one of the contact methods listed on our Website’s “Contact” page at www.spectralcore.com/contact. We will respond within thirty (30) days of receipt of your request.
Requests to Access Personal Data
If we grant your request to access personal data, we will: (1) confirm whether or not we are processing your personal data; (2) provide you with a copy of any of your personal data that we possess; and (3) provide you with information about how we process such data (e.g. purposes, categories, recipients, etc.).
Requests to Delete Data
If you request that we delete your personal data that we possess, we will do so unless: (1) the data is needed to exercise the right of freedom of expression; (2) we have a legal obligation to keep the data; (3) we must keep the data for reasons of public interest; or (4) the data has been processed so that it is anonymized.
Any personal data we processed unlawfully will be deleted. If you were a minor when we collected the personal data, we will delete the data upon request.
If we believe any third parties have acquired your personal data through us, we will take reasonable steps to inform them that you have requested erasure of such data.
Objections to Processing of Personal Data
If your request is an objection to the processing of your personal data for directing marketing purposes, we will cease using your data for such purposes.
As a general rule, we will comply with objections to processing personal data except: (1) where it is not technically or commercially feasible to do so; or (2) we have a legal obligation that overrides your individual rights and freedoms.
Portability Requests
If we collected personal data from you because of a contract between us or based on your consent, and we processed that data by automated means (in structured machine-readable format), you can request that data be transmitted by us to another company or organization.
We will provide such data to the recipient third party in a commonly used open format electronic file (e.g. CSV, JSON, XML, etc.).
Denied Requests
If we reject your request, we will provide you with the reason(s) for doing so. You may then choose to file a complaint with the Data Protection Authority and request a judicial remedy to the extent such a request is not in conflict with the laws of laws of the United Kingdom or the arbitration provisions of our website’s Terms and Conditions of Use).
Processing Fees
As a general rule, there is no fee for processing your GDPR request. However, we reserve the right to refuse your request or charge a reasonable fee for processing it if the request is manifestly unfounded or excessive. For example, it would be excessive to make a repetitive second request to access your personal data one month after we provided you with the data from a prior request.
Automated Processing
We may make decisions through automated processing (e.g. algorithms) of personal data that are legally binding or significantly affect you.
Any such automated decision-making is done per your express consent or because it is necessary for reasons of substantial public interest under applicable law.
Such an automated decision may be made based on relevant law. However, if the decision is made for other reasons, we will inform you of the process’ logic and potential consequences of the decision. To the extent that the GDPR does not conflict with the laws of the United Kingdom or the arbitration provisions found within our website’s Terms and Conditions of Use, you may also have a right to obtain human intervention and contest the automated decision.
11. Minors
We sell software subscriptions, licenses, and services to businesses. We do not knowingly provide services or sell products to children on our website. If you are less than eighteen (18) years old, you may use our website only with the permission, active involvement, and supervision of an adult parent or legal guardian.
IF YOU ARE A MINOR, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE US OR OTHER WEBSITE VISITORS WITH ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION.
12. This Policy Is Part of Our Terms and Conditions of Use
Our website privacy policy is a part of, and subject to, our website's Terms and Conditions of Use. You may view these terms and conditions on our Website.
13. This Policy and Customer Agreements
If you are our customer, any customer agreement (e.g. software subscription agreement) between us supersedes this policy to the extent there is any conflict with the terms and conditions of the customer agreement.
14. Policy Changes
The terms of this privacy policy may change from time to time. If such changes are made, we will notify you by a notice posted on our website's home page of the changes that have been made. If you disagree with the changes that have been made, please contact us by using one of the contact methods listed on our Website’s “Contact” page at www.spectralcore.com/contact. Any changes made to this policy will not apply to information we have collected from you prior to making the changes.
By continuing to access our website after changes to this privacy policy go into effect, you are agreeing to be legally bound by the revised policy.
If you are concerned about the topics covered by this website privacy policy, you should read it each time before you use our website.
15. Questions or Concerns
Any questions or concerns about this website privacy policy should be brought to our attention by using one of the contact methods listed on our Website’s “Contact” page at www.spectralcore.com/contact.
Solutions
Full Convert
Replicator
Omni Loader
Support
Documentation
Customer support
Company
© 2020 Spectral Core Ltd. All rights reserved.
